{
  "name": "",
  "isFavorite": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Shirt",
      "back": "Gömlek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "T-shirt",
      "back": "Tişört"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sweater",
      "back": "Kazak"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Jacket",
      "back": "Ceket"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Coat",
      "back": "Mont"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pants",
      "back": "Pantolon"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Jeans",
      "back": "Kot pantolon"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Shorts",
      "back": "Şort"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Skirt",
      "back": "Etek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Dress",
      "back": "Elbise"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Socks",
      "back": "Çorap"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Shoes",
      "back": "Ayakkabı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sneakers",
      "back": "Spor ayakkabı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Boots",
      "back": "Bot"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sandals",
      "back": "Sandalet"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hat",
      "back": "Şapka"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cap",
      "back": "Kasket"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Scarf",
      "back": "Atkı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Gloves",
      "back": "Eldiven"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Belt",
      "back": "Kemer"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tie",
      "back": "Kravat"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Suit",
      "back": "Takım elbise"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Blouse",
      "back": "Bluz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Underwear",
      "back": "İç çamaşırı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bra",
      "back": "Sütyen"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Swimsuit",
      "back": "Mayo"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pajamas",
      "back": "Pijama"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Raincoat",
      "back": "Yağmurluk"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hoodie",
      "back": "Kapüşonlu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Zipper",
      "back": "Fermuar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Button",
      "back": "Düğme"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pocket",
      "back": "Cep"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Collar",
      "back": "Yaka"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sleeve",
      "back": "Kol (giysi)"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Fabric",
      "back": "Kumaş"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Style",
      "back": "Stil"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Fashion",
      "back": "Moda"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Loose",
      "back": "Bol"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tight",
      "back": "Dar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "New",
      "back": "Yeni"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Old",
      "back": "Eski"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Clean",
      "back": "Temiz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Dirty",
      "back": "Kirli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Try on",
      "back": "Denemek (kıyafet)"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Wear",
      "back": "Giymek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Take off",
      "back": "Çıkarmak"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Fit",
      "back": "Uymak"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Size",
      "back": "Beden"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Color",
      "back": "Renk"
    }
  ]
}
